Reception. Can I help you?
Hello. Is this the Sheraton Hotel in Cairo?
Yes, sir.
Hi. I'm calling from La Prima Pizzeria in Bredäng out of Sweden in Stockholm.
And we have a spec... we have a special offer this week on a choice free pizza and a small sallad for 49 kronor only.
Yes, sir.
You will have pizza from here? From the Cairo Sheraton?
No no no no. We have it at La Prima Pizzeria in Bredäng out of Stockholm, Sweden.
Could you give me again, please, the ah ehh ... wha, what's ... [?].
The pizzeria name is La Prima Pizzeria.
La ... La Prima Pizzeria. Okay.
And choice free pizza, small salad.
Yes.
49 kronor. Swedish kronor.
49 ... okay.
I will, I will tell our guests, sir.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome. Bye.
Thank you.
Reservation of the noomi [?] help you?
Yes hello! I called a few minutes ago from La Prima Pizzeria in Bredäng, Stockholm.
And I have to point out that this does not include the special price pizzas. The special pizzas as the la prima or the flygande flopp with bearnaise sause.
Can, hold on. [?]
This is not included in the 49 kronor. I only wanted to forward that so you know. Okay!
Eh ... you want to make a reservation for a room?
No. I am informing about, if your, any of your guests are dropping by in Sweden you should know where to eat pizza.
Okay! Thank you. Good bye. Good bye.
Bye bye.